ん？　ぶぁピカ！
For inciting me... No need for small talk.
よかったね！ え？
You and I will play Gungi.
「クモ」が死んで…　これでやっと
Right now, I am learning the
rules, so you must wait.
一番したかったことに 集中できるね。 早く見つけてあげなきゃ 仲間達の目。
Huh? You don't sound like the Supreme Leader.
ゴン…。
He's dead.
うん！　もし　俺達に 手伝えることがあったら…。
Now I am the King. I'm s-so sorry!
ニヒっ。
Please forgive me!
こんの！ お前が　先にやったんだろ お返しだ。
I'm only a fool, one who knows
nothing of the outside world!
俺は　わざとじゃ　ない！ キルアは　わざとじゃないか！
I can't even talk normally...
えいっ。
You are distracting me. Be silent.
あっ　フッフフ。
Or I'll kill you.
いや　もう少し　いい時間帯に 品が出せたら　４億を超えた。
Okay, I basically understand.
くじ運が悪かった。
Let us begin.
真面目だな　お前さん。
What's wrong?
どんなに高く売れたって あんたに金は 入って来ねえんだろ？
It appears she's passed out.
そういう問題じゃねえ。
After you told her to be quiet,
she shut her mouth...
２人で持ち逃げすれば １人　１億７０００万だぜ。 ウフフフ…。
Then, since her nose was stuffed up,
it seems she was unable to breathe.
あんた　ホントに ゴンとキルアのダチか？
This is an uncommonly stupid girl.
[TEL] 冗談だよ。
Yeah, that was embarrassing!
もしもし　おう！　クラピカ！
I can't even do things a baby can.
久々に全員集合だね！ ああ！
Yes! I'm honored to play against you.
迫力みたいなもんが 出た気がするな。 そうか？
You can see with your eyes?
君は　大した変化もなさそうだな。
No, I can't see a thing.
ムカつく度も増したな　おい。
So would you please tell me your moves?
そういや　「旅団」の１人を 倒したらしいな。
I only open them when I play.
「念」を覚えて間もないお前が 一体どうやって？
If it bothers you, I can try to close them...
もし　お前達が 「クモ」の残党を捕らえたくて
I don't care.
それを聞きたいなら　やめておけ。 そのことだけじゃ　ないよ。 俺達だって 「念」を究めたいと思ってる。
The atmosphere has changed.
これから先も　念能力は 絶対に必要になると思うから。 なら　なおさら　やめておけ 私の話は　参考にはならない。
4-4-1, pawn.
何で？
You can't reach him at all?
私の能力は 「旅団」以外の者に使えない。
No, I guess his phone is off.
えっ？ 「制約と誓約」？
We agreed that he would initiate all contact, so I guess I shouldn't be surprised.
ああ　「念」は 精神が大きく影響する能力。
Damn, then we have to wait for him to call?
覚悟の量が力を上げる。 しかし　それは　同時に 高いリスクを伴う。
Why does that guy look like he
was born in the wrong decade?
私は　念能力の大半を 「クモ」打倒のために使うことを 誓った。
And the look on his face says
he's always looking for a fight...
そのために　ルールも決めた。 何だよ　そのルールってのは。 「クモ」でない者を 「念」の鎖で攻撃した場合
The other has no eyebrows, and that expression makes it
clear that he trusts no one.
私は　命を落とす。
It's not even a question of
whether he and I can get along.
あ…。 はぁ？　どういうこった？
I can already see he won't believe a word I say.
私の心臓には 「念」の刃が刺さったままだ。
Gon, I'm sorry to say that my
first impression is very bad!
ルールを破れば その刃が私の心臓を貫き　死ぬ。 これが　私のルールと覚悟 「制約と誓約」だ。
Unless I get some really good news soon, there's no way I'll be able to trust them. I guarantee it.
「クモ」以外には 全く通じない力だ。
Hey, what's all this?
お前達だから話した 他言は　しないでくれ。
Beats me. Just a pack of strays, I guess.
何で…　何で話したんだ！ そんな大事なことを！ えっ？
They have collars... He's been feeding all the animals
left behind due to the selection.
なぜだろうな…。
He's even sacrificed sleep...
「クモ」の頭が死んで 気が抜けたのかもしれない。
I'm not feeding all of them! I know we don't have time to waste on that!
マズいんだ　奴らの生き残りに 記憶を読む　女の能力者がいる。
So I abandoned those that stood no chance. That's efficient, yeah?
もし　あいつに このことがバレたら
Some were just skin and bones,
but still wouldn't take my food.
クラピカに勝ち目はなくなる！ でも　あの時はバレなかったよ？
Some were so loyal, they wouldn't leave
their homes after I untied them...
俺達も　奴らが捜している鎖野郎が クラピカだと知らなかったからな。 あ…。
What's so bad about saving
the ones that want the help?!
一度　調べてシロだと 思ったんだから。
You don't have to cry about it.
他にも　ノブナガって奴がいる こいつが　ヤバいんだ。
I'm n-not crying, fool!
クラピカを捜してるし 俺達を追うのも諦めていない。
Want me to smack you?
そいつは　お前らと クラピカとの接点を知ってるのか？ いや。
That won't be enough to raise my opinion.
なら　大丈夫だろ その記憶を探るって奴の周りに
Well, he certainly is different, though.
一応　協定は結んでいたが 奴の狙いだった 「クモ」の頭が死んだ今
7-8-2, spy. Checkmate.
どんな行動に出るかは 分からない。
She's using an orthodox approach,
stacking archers on her pawns.
どういうことだ？ 引き揚げるってのはよ。
Textbook execution. And her initial placement
is one used with beginners.
今夜で　お宝は　全部　頂ける それで終わりだ。
Meaning that I am not good enough
for her to show her true skill.
まだだろ。
Another game.
他に何がある？ 鎖野郎を捜し出す。
Yes, absolutely!
このまま　ウボォーの敵も取らず また　散り散りになるってのか？
8-8-1, knight.
ウボォーが退屈するだろうが。
I guess that's checkmate.
いいかげんにしねえか ノブナガ　団長命令だぞ。
You're such a fast learner, Supreme Leader.
ああ　団長命令は　絶対だ。 だが　そりゃホントに 団長としての命令か？
I'll have to step up my game,
or you'll get the jump on me!
クロロよ。
That's enough... Go get some rest.
ノブナガ　それは…。 うるせぇ！ 俺は　クロロに聞いている！
That isn't necessary... I'm just fine. I can play Gungi for three days
and nights without sleep!
その質問に答える前に
Once I've finished with him, it'll be your turn.
ノブナガ　俺の質問に答えろ。
Then I'll get a little rest.
生年月日は？ あぁ？
What do you think?
生まれた日だよ　いつだ？
It's but a matter of time.
７０年の９月８日だ。
There are more options to choose from, but essentially, this game is
no different than the rest.
血液型は？ Ｂ型だ。 名前は？ ノブナガ＝ハザマ！ 知ってんだろ！
In four or five more games, she will
have to use her real ability.
何なんだよ！ 次は　何が知りてぇんだ？
Once that happens, I shall be
able to observe her rhythm.
いや　もういい それをこの紙に書いてくれ。
Nothing has changed.
だったら　最初から 書かせりゃいいだろうが！
Your Majesty, the Go player hanged himself.
あぁ？　何だ？　こりゃ。 詩の形を借りた １００％当たる占い 予知能力だ。 ノストラードの娘から盗んだ。 １００％当たる占い？
While the King continues to play
against the Gungi master, a short distance away, Morel has
been using his power to surround
４行詩のそれぞれが 週ごとに起きることを 予言している。
the capital city of Peijing.
こっちは昨日　その娘に 俺が占ってもらったものだ。
He then envelops it in an aura haze, creating a smoke puppet that he can
control at will via the Nen within the core. His ability can sustain two hundred
and sixteen puppets at once.
この「大切な暦が欠けた」ってのは ひょっとして…。 ウボォーのことだ。
On the chance that the enemy retaliates,
I've made my soldiers more responsive, so I can only maintain fifty now.
その娘は ウボォーのことなど知らない。
But they're much stronger.
つまり　俺達が マフィアの競売を襲うってことは
One advantage is that En can't differentiate
そいつに予言されてたわけだ。
between one of these and a human.
そして　「十老頭」にも その予言のファンがいたらしい。
But at heart, Chimera Ants are still ants.
なるほど　それで 最初に襲った時
So Neferpitou won't leave the King's side.
オークションの品が 移されていたのも合点が行く。
As expected, Neferpitou has recalled
the controlled humans to the capital
ノブナガのは どんな占いが出たんですか？
to take up defensive positions.
自動書記といってな 俺には　内容は分からない。 ノブナガに聞けよ。
That implies the King's safety is top priority.
ノブナガ　どうなんだ？
Which means that restricting the movement
of the Royal Guard is very easy.
来週　恐らく　５人死ぬな。
However, the question is how the King will respond.
誰だ？　その５人って。 知らねえよ 俺にゃ　よく理解できねえ。
If we're dealing with a King who does as he
likes, it'll be harder to anticipate him.
辛うじて分かるのは ２番目の詩
And the risk of miscalculation increases.
蜘蛛の手足が半分に なってることくらいだ。
But as long as they keep
these coming, we're fine.
ウボォーの他 あと５人ってことだろ。
Long time, no see.
俺の占いにも同じように出ていた。
I've been looking for you. Bah, he's gotten stronger.
ちょっと　見せて。
The air about him feels totally different.
団長　ちょっと　私 占ってみてください。
Knuckle's APR is gone?
やっぱり　そうだ 来週　死ぬの　私です。
In the end, I will triumph.
マジか。
Time to return the favor.
うん　だって ２週目までしか　占い　ないもん。
First, I'll beat you down.
あとね　パクノダと シャルナークも死ぬよ。
Then it's the pompadour's turn.
ふん。 へぇ。
His confidence is far from baseless.
何で　パクノダと シャルナークって分かる？
He must have gained a new ability.
これね　暦の月が団員の番号を 表してるみたい。
I wouldn't be so certain!
「霜月」は　１１月 ウボォーの団員番号ね。
If that ability is to exorcise Nen,
we're in trouble.
「葉」が葉月　８月
Knuckle and Shoot both use
hit-and-fade fighting styles.
「涸れる」が水無月
Shoot does what he can to support
Knuckle's Chapter 7 Bankruptcy.
つまり６月を それぞれ暗示している。
But we can't nullify their Nen with ours
さらに　「涸れ落ちる」は 死を示すとみていいだろう。 「緋の眼」ってのが誰なのか 分かんないけど。
if they have someone who can dispel it.
俺達じゃ　ない 十中八九　鎖野郎のことだろ。
A strategy that might have worked
against the King is useless now.
緋の眼…　思い出した 目が赤くなる連中ね。
However... if he has the ability to exorcise Nen,
this is a good opportunity.
そういうことになるね。 そいつも死ぬってことか？
If I neutralize him here, Knuckle
and Shoot can use their powers.
分からんぜ　血だらけで 地に臥してるってだけじゃ。
I must fight...
ノブナガ　つまり このまま鎖野郎と　やり合うと 被害が大きいってこと 戦力半減だ。
I can't drop Deep Purple, so I'll have
to get by on my remaining aura.
俺やノブナガの能力は いくらでも代わりが利くけど
What?
シズクとパクノダは　レアなんだ。 「旅団」としては 失うわけにはいかない。
He's still relying on speed? There are plenty of ways to deal with
someone who only uses speed.
今日は　第１週目の土曜日。
Now you're "It."
今日中に俺達のホームに戻れば 来週　鎖野郎に会うことは まず　ないだろう。
Huh? What was that?
鎖野郎と　やり合わなければ
Wh-Where am I?
逆に１００％ この予言は成就しない。
A savannah? Did he teleport me?
ノブナガ　お前やウボォーは 「旅団」の特攻だ。 死ぬのも仕事の１つに含まれる。
If this is his new ability, a different Chimera Ant is the Nen exorcist. That's bad.
お前ら　進んで捨て石になることを 選んだんじゃなかったか？
Sure you should just be standing around? It's time to start
ああ…　そうだ。
this game of tag. Tag?
シズク　パク　シャルは 主に情報処理部隊。
We're in a field that I created.
俺達　全身の行動を補佐する いわば生命線だ。
Unless you touch me, you can't leave.
こいつらの盾になって守るのが お前の役目じゃないのか？ ああ　そうだ。
Your time limit is eight hours.
待ってよ。
Let's start!
見つかるかもしれないよ。
Hey!
どうする？
You can't leave without touching me!
俺達が　クラピカの秘密を知った以上 受け身でいると危険だ。
If I chase you, I'll never catch you.
俺かゴンが　またノブナガに 捕まったら　多分　逃げられない。 だけど　今ならクラピカがいる 奴らが地下に潜って
So I'm going to take my time.
今なら「クモ」のアジトも分かる。 モタモタしている間に 逃げちまうかもしれない。
Morel disappeared with the enemy!
動くなら早いほうがいい。
Cheetu has activated his power...
こうしている間にも　アジトから ずらかってるかもしれねえ。
I don't know what it does, but they
won't be back for eight hours.
あまり考えてる時間はないぜ。
The scenery is just a wall.
確かに　その女は 私にとって危険だが 奴らの頭が死んだ以上 私は　ゴンの言う通り
Looks like I'm in some kind of space
separated from the real world, like he said.
同胞達の目を取り戻すことに 専念するよ。 マジかよ！ ああ。
Seems to be about the size of a baseball field.
本当に　いいのかよ!? クラピカ本人が　そう決めたんだ。 これ以上　俺達がどうこう 口出すこっちゃねえだろ。
If I stopped Deep Purple, I could
break out of here with ease. However...
すまない　キルア　ありがとう。
First, is it even possible for me to stop
Deep Purple from within this space?
貴重な情報を教えてもらった。 [TEL]
Second, if I'm able to stop it, will that aura return to me here, in this space?
ヒソカからだ。 え？ 「死体はフェイク」。
The worst scenario would be one
in which I stop Deep Purple, but the aura can't reach me in this space.
クラピカ？ 死体はフェイクだ。 え!?
Once Deep Purple is halted, it can't be reactivated until
I've recovered the aura.
死体って　「旅団」のか？ ああ！ 「クモ」の死体はフェイクだ！
It's too risky to try.
確かに 具現化系の能力者なら可能だ。
I can't stop Deep Purple.
クソ！　何で　こんなことに 頭が回らなかったんだ！
At least, not yet.
事態は急変したぜ　どうする？
Are you finally ready to start?
うん！ ああ。 [TEL]
This way! Follow my lead!
センリツか　どうした？ [TEL]　コミュニティーが 「旅団」の残党狩りを断念したわ。
Hold on, you aren't gonna...
何!? 奴らが流星街の 出身だってことが分かったの。
You bet I am!
「十老頭」が　直々に 終戦命令を下したらしいわ。
It's a waste of time.
懸賞金も　全て白紙に戻すって。
You can't destroy the walls or the hourglass. There's only one way out.
懸賞金も白紙って　マジかよ…。
And that's to catch me. I can tell that
「旅団」が　流星街出身か。
Knuckle's Chapter 7 Bankruptcy
has weakened his power...
なるほど　今まで実体がつかめず
So then...
警察も捕まえられなかったのも それで納得が行くぜ。
Hey, what happens if I don't touch
you within the time limit?
流星街って？
Who knows?
社会的には存在しないとされてる 連中が住む街さ。
I have no obligation to answer that question.
そんな街があるの？
Naturally, of course not.
ああ　公式には 無人ってことになっているが
It appears there's more to this ability.
実際には　１０００万人近い 人間がいるといわれている。
I'm in for the long haul, then.
もともとは １５００年以上前に　つくられた
Wake me up in five hours.
廃棄物の処分地でな。 投棄されるゴミを 再利用することで
Are you mocking me?
何を捨てても許される場所でな
Go ahead, lose your temper.
ゴミは　もちろん　武器も人も。 そして　何を捨てても
It seems you don't understand your own power.
あそこの住人は その全てを受け入れる。
This isn't a battle of speed.
そんな異質な街　流星街で 生まれ育った連中の絆は
It's a battle of mental fortitude.
「他人より細く　家族より強い」と 聞く。 実は　ゴミと称して
Deep Purple is still active...
流星街に　大量の武器や 貴金属を援助する連中がいる。 それが マフィアンコミュニティーだ。
So the operation continues.
どういうこと？ だって　マフィアは「旅団」を…。 見返りとして　マフィアは 流星街から人材を得ていた。
Leol-sama, I've discovered another enemy.
社会的には存在しない人間をな。
It's a man in a suit, with black hair and glasses. Anyone else around?
犯罪には　うってつけだ。 本来なら　お互い蜜月関係にある マフィアンコミュニティーと
No, just the figures in white.
流星街の間を「旅団」が壊した。 だが　それでも
Those white figures are probably ordinary soldiers.
マフィアは流星街との関係を 選んだってわけだ。
But it's possible that the true leader
is concealed among them.
やめたほうがいい　見たら驚くよ。
I am becoming worried.
いいから見せて。 はいはい。
They've played many times, but
the King is nowhere near victory.
「赤目の客が訪れて」。 「月達の秘密を」。
I should have been able to break
her defenses from the left side.
「月達」って俺達のことだよな？ ヒソカ　これは…。
But she used a peculiar move
sequence to turn the tables.
ヒソカ。
Impossible.
てめぇ　売ったのか？
From start to checkmate, there were
one hundred, forty-four moves.
ウボォーを！
This outcome could have only happened
if she foresaw each of my moves.
パクノダの手に渡ると同時に 内容が変わったヒソカの占い
This is utterly impossible!
それが意味するものとは 一体
A storm is brewing. The girl's strength upsets the King.